http://www.feridies.com/privacy

COVID-19 Update
We recommend youOrder by December 14thfor Christmas Delivery
Home/privacy
Privacy Policy
Security and Privacy
At FERIDIES, we recognize and respect the importance of maintaining the privacy of our customers. We pride ourselves on consistently providing our customers with quality products and excellent customer service. We gather personal information to allow us to process your orders efficiently as well as to provide an enhanced and more personalized shopping experience.
What Information We Gather & Why
When you place an order with us or request a catalog, we collect Personal Information such as your name, street or P.O. Box, city, state, zip code, phone number, FAX number, e-mail address, and credit card number. This information is used to process your orders efficiently or send you a catalog. If you do not wish to receive our mail order catalog, please let us know by sending an e-mail to customerservice@feridies.com, calling us at 1-866-732-6883 or to writing us.
The e-mail address you provide us is used to verify receipt of your Internet Order and to confirm shipment of the Order. When we have a question with an Internet Order, we first try to contact you using your e-mail address. If we are unable to get in touch with you or if the order needs to be shipped as soon as possible, we will contact you using the telephone number you provided us. You will only receive telephone contact from us regarding orders you have placed with our company.
On occasion, the personal information you give us may be shared with reputable third parties. This information will be used to make our future marketing efforts more efficient. This information may also be used by our marketing partners to bring you offers of interest. If you prefer not to receive these offerings, please let us know by sending an e-mail to customerservice@feridies.com, calling us at 1-866-732-6883 or writing to us at the address listed below.
Security
Security remains the primary concern for our on-line customers. When you shop with us via the website, your order information is encrypted using a secure session established with Secure Socket Layer (SSL). We protect your personal information, including your credit card number using industry-standard encryption technology which scrambles the characters you type, making it almost impossible for a third party to intercept this information as it travels over the Internet. It is our goal to serve you efficiently without exposing you to risks concerning unauthorized access to order transaction information.
Questions?
If you have any questions or concerns regarding the FERIDIES Privacy Policy, you can contact us by sending an e-mail to customerservice@feridies.com, calling us at 1-866-732-6883 or writing to us at:
Customer Service Department
FERIDIES
P.O. Box 186
Courtland, VA 23837
FERIDIES reserves the right to modify the privacy policy at its discretion. Any changes to the Privacy Policy will be posted on this website so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we may disclose it.
Sign up for our Email Newsletter
© Copyright 2020 FERIDIES. All Rights.
